pikby.com 2019-03-21

# Privacy Policy

**Last updated in September 2018.**

At Pikby, data privacy and data security are very important to us and we want to make sure that you trust us with your information. 

This Privacy Policy ("Policy") describes what type of information Pikby may collect, how we use it, how we share it with others, how we protect it and how you can access and control it. 

It also sets out how you can contact us if you have any queries or concerns regarding your personal data. 

If you have any questions or complaints about this Policy and our data protection processes, please get in touch with us at the contact mentioned below. 

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. Please check the Privacy Policy periodically for changes, although, if you are our customer, we may also notify you via email of any changes that, in our sole discretion, materially impact your use of the Services or the way we process your personal data. Your continued use of our Services which are subject to this Privacy Policy will signify your acceptance of any and all changes to this Privacy Policy made by us from time to time. 

This Privacy Policy is issued by Myrica LLC, with its registered office at, 2277 Progress Way, New York 10001, NY, United States. 

### Definitions

"Pikby", "we", "us", "our" means Myrica LLC and its subsidiaries Myrica LLC and Myrica GmbH.   
"Websites" means any website operated by Myrica LLC.   
"Services" means any product or other service that is operated by Myrica LLC.   
"Visitors" means any individual that visits our Websites, but that we can't identify yet.   
"Leads" means any Visitor of our Websites that has provided us with identifiable information (e.g., by filling a form on a landing page).   
"Users", "Customers" means any individual who has an account with any Myrica LLC Services.   
"GDPR" means the General Data Protection Regulation.   
Beside these specific definitions we will use the meanings as defined in the GDPR regulation. 

### 1\. What Information We Collect About you

#### 1.1. Information you provide to us

**1.1.1. Information you provide through our Websites**   
In specific cases you provide data to us through our Websites. For example, you provide your contact details when you sign up for our newsletter, download a white paper from one of our landing pages, use our free statistics sections or when you fill a contact form. 

**1.1.2. Information you provide through our Services**   
You provide data to us when you use our Services. For example, you provide us with information, when you sign up for an account, when you add new users, when you add notes or comments or when you use our Services on an ongoing basis as part of the general features of the Services. For some data that you provide in regards of the Services we are the data processor and you are the data controller. For this purpose we will sign a data processing agreement (DPA) with you, if needed. If you would like to sign such agreement, please get in touch with us at dataprivacy@quintly.com. 

**1.1.3. Information you provide through our support channels or direct communication**   
Through our support channels (e.g., Helpdesk, live chat) and direct email communication you provide us with data about yourself and about the case for which you are contacting us. 

**1.1.4. Payment information**   
When setting up a paid account with our Services, you provide us with payment information that allow us to charge you on a recurring basis. 

#### 1.2. Information We Collect Automatically

**1.2.1 Cookies and other tracking technologies** Cookies are small pieces of text sent by your web browser by a website you visit. A cookie file is stored in your web browser and allows the Websites or a third-party to recognize you and make your next visit easier and the Websites more useful to you. 

We use cookies and other tracking technologies in order to provide our Services, give you a better website experience and to improve our Websites and Services. In our cookie policy you can get more information and see the list of cookies/integrations/tags that we have implemented within our Services. This includes the use of third-party analytics services like Google Analytics, Hubspot and others. 

**1.2.2. Information on how you use our Services**   
When you visit and interact with our Services we collect certain information in the background in order to optimize and improve the Services going forward. This includes for example things like device and connection information, log data, logins, page views, API calls (Application Programming Interface), usage of specific features and error logging. 

### 2\. How We Use Information That We Collect

We use the personal data you provided to us only for specific purposes of the corresponding processing activities and only where we have legal bases to do so (in compliance with the GDPR article 6). Once the purpose for a processing activity is not applicable anymore, we will delete the data accordingly (for specifics please read the section on this topic below). In the following sections we list the specific areas in which we use your personal data. For even more transparency we have created a separate list of all our processing activities including the legal bases for processing that involve visitors, leads or users/customers. 

#### 2.1. Providing of our Websites

We use information you delivered to us in order to provide our Websites, including customer support, log files, rendering fonts and to operate and maintain the Websites. We also use your data in order to personalize your experience. 

#### 2.2. Providing of our Services

We use information you gave to us in order to provide our Services, including for account creation, authentication, customer support, log files, rendering fonts and to operate and maintain the Services. We also use your data in order to personalize your experience. 

### 3\. Communicating With You About Our Services

We use your contact information in order to communicate with you about our services. For example, we send you emails for confirmations, customer support, updates to the Services, technical notices and security measures. 

#### 3.1. Contact form

When you fill a contact form on our Websites, we use the data to get in touch with you to resolve your case. 

#### 3.2. Cookies And Other Tracking Technologies

We use your information in combination with cookies and tracking technologies with the goal of providing you an improved Websites and Services experience. 

**3.2.1. Cookies**

We use cookies to store information and identify you across our various web properties. For example, to identify you in our Services or to track your activity in order to improve the Websites and Services. You can find the full list of cookies in our cookie policy.

**3.2.2. Web analytics**

We use data that we gathered through web analytics scripts that we embed in our Websites and Services. For example, we use Google Analytics and Hubspot to analyze user behavior with the goal to improve the Websites and Services.

#### 3.3. Safety And Security

We use information about you to increase the safety and security of our Websites and Services. For example for verifying your account, detecting fraudulent activities and anything else that would make our Services more secure.

### 4\. How We Share Information We Collect

####  4.1. Service providers and third parties 

We work with third-party service providers for various tasks within our organization, including billing, marketing, customer support, analysis, accounting and others. If we transfer your personal data to a service provider in order to fulfill a task, we will make sure that the service provider only processes the data based on our instructions and by guaranteeing the same safeguards as we do. On top of that we guarantee that we have signed a data processing agreement with every service provider that makes sure that the partner is bound to the strict rules under the GDPR law. 

####  4.2. Law enforcement and compliance 

We will share your information with a third-party (including law enforcement authorities) if we believe that sharing is necessary to comply with any applicable law or governmental requests. 

####  4.3. Non-personal information 

In rare cases we may share non-personal data, such as aggregated information, with third-parties, including for reporting obligations and business/marketing purposes. 

### 5\. How We Secure Information We Collect

We use robust and state-of-the-art technical and organizational measures to secure the data that we have about you. For more details you can find our separate document on technical and organizational measures here. We are reviewing our data protection processes regularly in order to make sure that we protect your data in the best possible way. If we use sub contractors and service providers to fulfill a specific task based on your data, we will make sure that the partner has similar state-of-the-art data protection processes in place. 

### 6\. How Long We Store Your Information

We store your data only for as long as we need access to it in order to fulfill the purpose of the specific data processing activity. As the data retention period is different from use case to use case we have created a separate document with all our processing activities, in which you can find the exact period for each of the processing activities that we perform. On top of that and where possible we have applied a general rule inside Quintly that all personal data should be deleted or anonymized if you haven't been using our Websites and Services for more than 9 months. Exceptions to this rules only apply if there are technical limitations to guarantee this or where specific laws expect from us that we store the data for a longer time (e.g., requirements from tax authorities for storing documents).
